ctreal.com 2011-05-16

# Privacy Policy

|   |  |   
  
---  
  
CTMLS Privacy Policy:  

We recognize the importance of protecting the personal information you provide at web sites owned and/or controlled by the CONNECTICUT MULTIPLE LISTING SERVICE, INC. (CTMLS). We maintain the following privacy policy:  

  1. We may gather the following types of information needed to process your transactions, fulfill your requests, and maintain our membership records: 
    * Contact information you provide (for example, your email address as your unique identifier for you to recover search information you requested be saved by CTMLS.
    * Tracking information which our web server automatically recognizes each time you visit one of our sites or communicate with us by e-mail (for example your domain name, your e-mail address, and what pages you visit); and   
 
  2. We may use this information to: 
    * Improve and customize the content and layout of our sites and other communications tools.
    * Track usage of our sites.
    * Identify abuse or misuse of our sites.
    * Assist local and state REALTOR® associations and affiliated institutes, and societies in membership tracking and for their use for purposes similar to those listed above.   
 
  3. CTMLS does not share, sell or trade e-mail addresses.   
 
  4. Some of our sites may contain advertising placed by advertising networks pursuant to agreements between the CTMLS and the advertising network. We do not control these advertising networks, the sites of third parties reached through links on our site or their information collection practices and CTMLS will not be responsible for the activities of these third parties. The advertising network uses cookies to collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you click on the banner ads appearing on our sites. This information is collected by the advertising network for purposes of measuring and reporting on the advertising to advertisers and CTMLS. The advertising network may also aggregate the information for certain other statistical and reporting purposes.   
 
  5. If a property that you own is listed or otherwise included in our database, please be advised that you must contact the real estate broker through whom you listed your property on the market. Except for very limited situations, CTMLS has no authority to remove a listing posted by a real estate broker from this CTMLS Web Site, nor can CTMLS intervene in the legal arrangements between real estate brokers and their clients.
